Faculty Reference Collection
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Gilbert, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1043 (Box 14, Folder 50)
- Gilbert, Linda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1044 (Box 14, Folder 51)
- Gilbert, Virginia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1045 (Box 14, Folder 52)
- Gilchrist, Eugene A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1046 (Box 14, Folder 53)
- Giles, Freda Scott, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1047 (Box 14, Folder 54)
- Gillis, Carolyn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1048 (Box 14, Folder 55)
- Gilliam, James F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1049 (Box 14, Folder 56)
- Gillispie, Gregory D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1050 (Box 14, Folder 57)
- Gilman, Charlote P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1051 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Gilman, Irvin, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1052 (Box 14, Folder 59)
- Gilman, Irvin E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1053 (Box 14, Folder 60)
- Ginsberg, Allen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1054 (Box 14, Folder 61)
- Ginsberg, Warren, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1055 (Box 14, Folder 62)
- Ginsberg, Warren, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1056 (Box 14, Folder 63)
- Gioia, Vito, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1057 (Box 14, Folder 64)
- Giovane, Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1058 (Box 14, Folder 65)
- Gisdfi, Anthony, 1964 September-1976 June 10; nam_ua950.003-1059 (Box 14, Folder 66)
- Glanz, Joseph, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1060 (Box 14, Folder 67)
- Gmelch, George J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1061 (Box 14, Folder 68)
- Gjaja, Vesna, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1062 (Box 14, Folder 69)
- Glass, Julia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1063 (Box 14, Folder 70)
- Glover, Douglas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1064 (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Glover, Douglas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1065 (Box 14, Folder 72)
- Gluck, Robert J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1066 (Box 14, Folder 73)
- Goatley, Virginia, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1067 (Box 14, Folder 74)
- Goel, Sanjay, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1068 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Goggin, Mary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1069 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Gold, Maxine S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1070 (Box 14, Folder 77)
- Gold, Steven D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1071 (Box 14, Folder 78)
- Golden, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1072 (Box 14, Folder 79)
- Goldfarb, Owen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1073 (Box 14, Folder 80)
- Goldin, Liliana, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1074 (Box 14, Folder 81)
- Goldman, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1075 (Box 14, Folder 82)
- Goldman, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1076 (Box 14, Folder 83)
- Goldsberry, Lisa James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1077 (Box 14, Folder 84)
- Goldstein, Ken, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1078 (Box 14, Folder 85)
- Goldstein, Phyllis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1079 (Box 14, Folder 86)
- Goldstein, Richard Z., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1080 (Box 14, Folder 87)
- Goldstein, Walter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1081 (Box 14, Folder 88)
- Goldstein, Walter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1082 (Box 14, Folder 89)
- Gonzalez, Henry R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1083 (Box 14, Folder 90)
- Gonzalez, Lisa, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1084 (Box 14, Folder 91)
- Goodman, Carl F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1085 (Box 14, Folder 92)
- Goodman, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1086 (Box 14, Folder 93)
- Goodman, Richard A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1087 (Box 14, Folder 94)
- Goodwin, Danny, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1088 (Box 14, Folder 95)
- Gootzeit, Michael J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1089 (Box 14, Folder 96)
- Gordis, Elana, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1090 (Box 14, Folder 97)
- Gordon, Gilbert, 1968 February 28; nam_ua950.003-1091 (Box 14, Folder 98)
- Gordon, Hugh, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1092 (Box 14, Folder 99)
- Gordon, Hugh, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1093 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Gordon, Hugh, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1094 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Gordon, Hugh, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1095 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Gordon, Leonard V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1096 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Gordon, Leonard Victor, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1097 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Gordon, Vivian, 1985; nam_ua950.003-1098 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Gossen, Eleanor, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1099 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Gossen, Eleanor Adam, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1100 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Gossen, Gary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1101 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Gottfredson, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1102 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Gottschalk, Nathan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1103 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Gould, Josiah B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1104 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Gould, Samuel B., 1963-1970; nam_ua950.003-1105 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Grainger, Anthony, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1106 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Gouraige, Ghislain, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1107 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Gradus, Nora, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1108 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Grava, Arnolds, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1109 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Grava, Arnolds, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1110 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Grava, Arnolds, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1111 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Green, Jerry E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1112 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Green, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1113 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Green, John Arthur, 1975 February 10; nam_ua950.003-1114 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Green, Matie E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1115 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Green, Michael, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1116 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Green, Suzanne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1117 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Greenberg, J. Mayo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1118 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Greenberg, J. Mayo, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1119 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Greene, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1120 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Greenfeld, Norman, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1121 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Greenfield, Norman, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1122 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Greenwold, Mark, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1123 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Gregg, Lois Hamilton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1124 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Gregory, Kim, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1125 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Greiman, Jennifer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1126 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Grenander, M.E. (Mary Elizabeth), 1918-1988; nam_ua950.003-1127 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- Grenander, M.E. (Mary Elizabeth), Undated; nam_ua950.003-1128 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- Grenander, M.E. (Mary Elizabeth), Undated; nam_ua950.003-1129 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Griffith, Glynne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1130 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Griggs-Janower, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1131 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Griggs-Janower, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1132 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Grignon, Albina, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1133 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Grignon, Albina, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1134 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Grimes, William V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1135 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Grimes, William V. Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1136 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Groark, James J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1137 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Groark, James, 1992; nam_ua950.003-1138 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Groark, James J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1139 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Groat, Douglas F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1140 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Gronberg, Dianne I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1141 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Gronberg, Dianne I., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1142 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Grondahl, Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1143 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Grossberg, Daniel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1144 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Grossberg, Millie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1145 (Box 15, Folder 53)
- Gruenewald, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1146 (Box 15, Folder 54)
- Gruner, William J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1147 (Box 15, Folder 55)
- Grupta, Ravindra, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1148 (Box 15, Folder 56)
- Guarino, Eugene, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1149 (Box 15, Folder 57)
- Guarino, Eugene A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1150 (Box 15, Folder 58)
- Guarino, Eugene A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1151 (Box 15, Folder 59)
- Guastello, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1152 (Box 15, Folder 60)
- Guha, Susanta R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1153 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Guha, Susanta R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1154 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Guha, Susanta R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1155 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Guha, Susanta R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1156 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Guha, Susanta R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1157 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Guidotti, Don, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1158 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Guithart, Jorge, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1159 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Gullahorn, Jean, 1986; nam_ua950.003-1160 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Gullahorn, Jean, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1161 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Gullotta, Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1162 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Gummer, Burton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1163 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Gunn, John Martynn, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1164 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Gunnell, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1165 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Gunnell, John G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1166 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Gunnell, John G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1167 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Guney, Senem, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1168 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Gurney, Kathleen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1169 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Gustina, David, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1170 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Haas, Andrew, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1171 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Haas, Shari, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1172 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Haase, Richard F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1173 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Haber, Judith P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1174 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Haberer, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1175 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Haberl, Arthur, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1176 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Haboush, William J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1177 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Hagan, Georgette, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1178 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Hagan, Jan L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1179 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Haggerty, John P., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1180 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Hahner, June, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1181 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Haile, Christine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1182 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Haile, Christine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1183 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Haine, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1184 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Haines, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1185 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Hairston, Creasie F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1186 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Haldar, Pradeep, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1187 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Haldowski, Timothy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1188 (Box 16, Folder 36)
- Hale, Clarence F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1189 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Hall, Kermit, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1190 (Box 16, Folder 38)
- Hall, Kermit, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1191 (Box 16, Folder 39)
- Hall, Kermit, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1192 (Box 16, Folder 40)
- Hall, Kermit, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1193 (Box 16, Folder 41)
- Hall, Kermit L., 1944-2006; nam_ua950.003-1194 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Hall, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1195 (Box 16, Folder 43)
- Hallenbeck, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1196 (Box 16, Folder 44)
- Hallenbeck, James Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1197 (Box 16, Folder 45)
- Halpern, Leslie Fay, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1198 (Box 16, Folder 46)
- Halter, Helen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1199 (Box 16, Folder 47)
- Haltzel, Helen N., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1200 (Box 16, Folder 48)
- Hamberg, Marie, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1201 (Box 16, Folder 49)
- Hamdi, Mary Evans, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1202 (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Hamilton, Harry, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1203 (Box 16, Folder 51)
- Hamilton, Harry Lemuel Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1204 (Box 16, Folder 52)
- Hamilton, La Verne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1205 (Box 16, Folder 53)
- Hamlin, Walter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1206 (Box 16, Folder 54)
- Hamm, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1207 (Box 16, Folder 55)
- Hammer, Peter, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1208 (Box 16, Folder 56)
- Hammond, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1209 (Box 16, Folder 57)
- Hammond, William, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1210 (Box 16, Folder 58)
- Hanani, Yehuda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1211 (Box 16, Folder 59)
- Hancock, Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1212 (Box 16, Folder 60)
- Hancock, Charles R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1213 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Handy, Ernest V., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1214 (Box 16, Folder 62)
- Hanes, Steven, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1215 (Box 16, Folder 63)
- Hanft, Richard A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1216 (Box 16, Folder 64)
- Hanifan, Jil, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1217 (Box 16, Folder 65)
- Hanks, Jane, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1218 (Box 16, Folder 66)
- Hanley, Jerome, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1219 (Box 16, Folder 67)
- Hannan, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1220 (Box 16, Folder 68)
- Hannay, Margaret, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1221 (Box 16, Folder 69)
- Hanner, Martha, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1222 (Box 16, Folder 70)
- Hannigan, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1223 (Box 16, Folder 71)
- Hannigan, John H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1224 (Box 16, Folder 72)
- Hanson, David J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1225 (Box 16, Folder 73)
- Hanson, Pat, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1226 (Box 16, Folder 74)
- Hardiman, Eric, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1227 (Box 16, Folder 75)
- Harding, Constance J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1228 (Box 16, Folder 76)
- Harding, Constance Joy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1229 (Box 16, Folder 77)
- Hardt, Robert H., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1230 (Box 16, Folder 78)
- Hardt, Sandy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1231 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Hardy, William G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1232 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Hardford, Jon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1233 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Hargett, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1234 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Hargett, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1235 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Harmon, Thomas, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1236 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Harper, Gregory, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1237 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Harper, Gregory, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1238 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Harrington, Charles F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1239 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Harrington, Jack, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1240 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Harrington, Susan M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1241 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Harris, Ann, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1242 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Harris, Carolyn Williams, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1243 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Harris, Carolyn Williams, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1244 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Harris, Carolyn Williams, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1245 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Harris, Joanne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1246 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Harris, Rachel S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1247 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Harrison, Lee, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1248 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Harrison, Teresa, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1249 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Harrison, T. Mark, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1250 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Harrison, Timothy M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1251 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Hart, Amy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1252 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Hart, Rodney A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1253 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Hartgen, David T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1254 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Hartigan, John A., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1255 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Hartley, John, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1256 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Hartman, Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1257 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Hartmark, Leif, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1258 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Hartzell, Karl Drew, Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1259 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Haskins, Motier, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1260 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Hastings, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1261 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Hastings, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1262 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Hastings, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1263 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Hathaway, Eleanor R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1264 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Hathaway, Eleanor Roth, 1948 January 15; nam_ua950.003-1265 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Haugard, Jeffrey J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1266 (Box 17, Folder 36)
- Hauser, Frank, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1267 (Box 17, Folder 37)
- Hauser, Richard S., 1948-1996; nam_ua950.003-1268 (Box 17, Folder 38)
- Hauser, Richard S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1269 (Box 17, Folder 39)
- Hauser, Muriel, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1270 (Box 17, Folder 40)
- Havens, Janet M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1271 (Box 17, Folder 41)
- Haviland, Morrison, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1272 (Box 17, Folder 42)
- Haviland, Morrison C., 1972; nam_ua950.003-1273 (Box 17, Folder 43)
- Hawkins, Lester G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1274 (Box 17, Folder 44)
- Hawkins, Lester G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1275 (Box 17, Folder 45)
- Hayes, John T., 1984; nam_ua950.003-1276 (Box 17, Folder 46)
- Hays, Samuel H., 1970-1988; nam_ua950.003-1277 (Box 17, Folder 47)
- Hayward, Horton, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1278 (Box 17, Folder 48)
- Hazard, Brenda, 1989; nam_ua950.003-1279 (Box 17, Folder 49)
- Head, Brian F., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1280 (Box 17, Folder 50)
- Healey, James J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1281 (Box 17, Folder 51)
- Heaphey, James, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1282 (Box 17, Folder 52)
- Heaphey, James J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1283 (Box 17, Folder 53)
- Heaphey, Joan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1284 (Box 17, Folder 54)
- Hearst, George, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1285 (Box 17, Folder 55)
- Hebert, Andy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1286 (Box 17, Folder 56)
- Hebert, Lloyd, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1287 (Box 17, Folder 57)
- Hechinger, Fred, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1288 (Box 17, Folder 58)
- Hedberg, Bill, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1289 (Box 17, Folder 59)
- Hedge, Krishna G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1290 (Box 17, Folder 60)
- Hedges, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1291 (Box 17, Folder 61)
- Hedges, Roman B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1292 (Box 17, Folder 62)
- Heighton, Paula-Christy, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1293 (Box 17, Folder 63)
- Heikoff, Joseph M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1294 (Box 17, Folder 64)
- Heimberg, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1295 (Box 17, Folder 65)
- Heimberg, Richard G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1296 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Heiser, Wayne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1297 (Box 17, Folder 67)
- Heiser, W. Wayne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1298 (Box 17, Folder 68)
- Heiss, Ann M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1299 (Box 17, Folder 69)
- Heller, Charles, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1300 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Heller, Frieda, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1301 (Box 17, Folder 71)
- Helmrich, Dennis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1302 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Helmrich, Dennis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1303 (Box 17, Folder 73)
- Helsby, Robert D., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1304 (Box 17, Folder 74)
- Hemenway, Curtis L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1305 (Box 17, Folder 75)
- Hemenway, Curtis L., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1306 (Box 17, Folder 76)
- Henderson, Floyd, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1307 (Box 17, Folder 77)
- Henderson, Floyd M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1308 (Box 17, Folder 78)
- Henderson, Floyd M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1309 (Box 17, Folder 79)
- Hendricks, Mike, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1310 (Box 17, Folder 80)
- Henighan, John G., 1969-1994; nam_ua950.003-1311 (Box 17, Folder 81)
- Hennessy, Rosemary, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1312 (Box 17, Folder 82)
- Hennett, Alisha, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1313 (Box 17, Folder 83)
- Henrikson, Craig, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1314 (Box 17, Folder 84)
- Henrikson, Craig, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1315 (Box 17, Folder 85)
- Henrikson, Craig Ernest, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1316 (Box 17, Folder 86)
- Henrikson, Craig Ernest, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1317 (Box 17, Folder 87)
- Henry, Jon, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1318 (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Herbst, Susan, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1319 (Box 17, Folder 89)
- Herkowitz, Gloria, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1320 (Box 17, Folder 90)
- Herkowitz, Gloria M., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1321 (Box 17, Folder 91)
- Herlands, Marty, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1322 (Box 17, Folder 92)
- Herlihy, John G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1323 (Box 17, Folder 93)
- Herman, Catherine, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1324 (Box 17, Folder 94)
- Herman, Robert S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1325 (Box 17, Folder 95)
- Herman, Robert S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1326 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Herman, Robert S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1327 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Hernandez, Browdy Jennifer, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1328 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Hernandez, Donald, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1329 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Herriott, Arthur W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1330 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Herron, Bruce, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1331 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Herzel, Roger, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1332 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Herzel, Roger W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1333 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Herzig, Abbe, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1334 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Herzog, Bette R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1335 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Herzstein, Robert, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1336 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Hester, Donald G., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1337 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Hester, Richard, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1338 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Heter, Frank E., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1339 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Hewat, Nancy C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1340 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Hewitt, Ryland H., Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1341 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Hewitt, Ryland Hugh, Jr., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1342 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Hickox, Edward, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1343 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Hicks, Scott, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1344 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Higginbotham, James T., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1345 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Higgins, A.C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1346 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Higgins, Albert C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1347 (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Higgins, Brian, 1988 April 21; nam_ua950.003-1348 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Hildreth, Anne, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1349 (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Hildebrand, Martin Victor, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1350 (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Hill, Inez, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1351 (Box 18, Folder 26)
- Hill, Johnetta, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1352 (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Hill, LaMar, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1353 (Box 18, Folder 28)
- Hill, Mike, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1354 (Box 18, Folder 29)
- Hillebrand, Gary R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1355 (Box 18, Folder 30)
- Hilles, Carolyn R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1356 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Hindelang, Michael J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1357 (Box 18, Folder 32)
- Hindley, Clarence B., 1952 June 24; nam_ua950.003-1358 (Box 18, Folder 33)
- Hines, Edward R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1359 (Box 18, Folder 34)
- Hindeling, Michael J., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1360 (Box 18, Folder 35)
- Hirsch, Helmut V.B., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1361 (Box 18, Folder 36)
- Hirsch, Helmut, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1362 (Box 18, Folder 37)
- Hirschenson, Cheryl, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1363 (Box 18, Folder 38)
- Hirschi, Travis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1364 (Box 18, Folder 39)
- Hirschi, Travis, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1365 (Box 18, Folder 40)
- Hirtle, Shephen C., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1366 (Box 18, Folder 41)
- Hitchcock, Arthur A., 1966; nam_ua950.003-1367 (Box 18, Folder 42)
- Hitchcock, Arthur, 1966; nam_ua950.003-1368 (Box 18, Folder 43)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 1991; nam_ua950.003-1369 (Box 18, Folder 44)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 1992-1993; nam_ua950.003-1370 (Box 18, Folder 45)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 1995; nam_ua950.003-1371 (Box 18, Folder 46)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 1996; nam_ua950.003-1372 (Box 18, Folder 47)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 1997; nam_ua950.003-1373 (Box 18, Folder 48)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 2001; nam_ua950.003-1374 (Box 18, Folder 49)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1375 (Box 18, Folder 50)
- Hitchcock, Karen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1376 (Box 18, Folder 51)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1377 (Box 18, Folder 52)
- Hitchcock, Karen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1378 (Box 18, Folder 53)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1379 (Box 18, Folder 54)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 2002; nam_ua950.003-1380 (Box 18, Folder 55)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 2003; nam_ua950.003-1381 (Box 18, Folder 56)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 2004; nam_ua950.003-1382 (Box 18, Folder 57)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1383 (Box 18, Folder 58)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1384 (Box 18, Folder 59)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1385 (Box 18, Folder 60)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1386 (Box 18, Folder 61)
- Hitchcock, Karen R., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1387 (Box 18, Folder 62)
- Hitchcock, Karen, 1996 April 24; nam_ua950.003-1388 (Box 18, Folder 63)
- Hitchcock, Karen, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1389 (Box 18, Folder 64)
- Ho, Paul, Undated; nam_ua950.003-1390 (Box 18, Folder 65)
- Hoagland, John S., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1391 (Box 18, Folder 66)
- Hobbs, Gary W., Undated; nam_ua950.003-1392 (Box 18, Folder 67)